Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org
Subs by Yeshwanth
I'm Peter Parker.
You don't know me. but I'll tell you something
which will seem just crazy to you.
However. it's true.
And I know that you will believe me. because you
you always know when I'm lying to you.
Eva. will you check the calibration of the matrix? She
not centered.
Checking calibration.
Eva. let's take a break.
Pause.
We know each other.
We were together.
But there was going to be a disaster and we
prevented it by making sure that both
I was forgotten.
First day at university. we're rocking it! This
crazy. we did it!
Oh God. I beg you! I'm including you.
What. today is not the most beautiful day in
your life?
After all. I'm not just Peter Parker.
I'm Spider-Man.
Listen to me.
I'm telling you.
And sometimes Spiderman complicates things
even if it breaks Peter's heart
Parker. They have a strange accent.
Well. really.
Maybe it's my responsibility.
Keep this secret to yourself.
But the truth is that I love you. M.
Jay.
And I hope that deep down you don't
I forgot that you love me too.
Supposedly this is the average speed.
But for now I'm Spider-Man.
Here I am!
Hey. okay!
What now?
Yesterday. members of an authoritative criminal
syndicate were defeated by Man
-a spider.
Hi. we live on the same floor.
Oh cool.
Nobody came here?
Only those who like the atmosphere. We
We use it to accumulate garbage.
Yes. great.
Hello family. Ned. student first
course. Came back more mature. more
wiser. more stylish.
And you be there.
Whoa. what's on the chin? Like?
I don’t know. you’re like a gig with a book.
Forward. forward!
Are you sure about this?
Did you miss me. Spider-Man?
If you fall from such a height. for
How long will it take for spit to reach you?
I don't know. you tell me.
Let's end on a good note.
To be continued...
Danny! What's happened?
Dewulf! All the evidence is in the trunk
his cars.
Do you want to steal my work?
No. You mean. I'm a volunteer.
A completely new New York. Thanks
Spider-Man is crime-heavy
fell.
The police attribute this success to the hero in
uterus. Let's run the test.
Armed attack on the base. For
he destroyed the last six months
all the top crime lords
cities. not to mention heavy-duty
ninja group.
The pride of New York.
The hero that adults count on
and who dreams of becoming a child.
Last semester at university.
Go crazy. We have graduation in
month. So many cool memories. C
what to start with?
Night swims in the Charles River with Jim and
Wally.
Famous Banana Food Parties
Lounge.
Sleepless nights playing poker with M.J.
and Nate Dog.
I remember sitting on the roof with M.J. and we
dreamed of coming here. It was like
yesterday. I still can't believe that we
were able to.
I'm so lucky to have made so many friends.
I wouldn't go through this with anyone else.
Listen.
Do you think someone is watching us? Well I
I don't even know. Maybe he is watching.
Okay. hi. if anyone is there.
No!
Yes.
it's in the very center of Brooklyn. in the middle
broad daylight.
Judging by this advertisement. this is the work of
Phosphol.
Yes. I'm not arguing. but is there evidence?
Yes. yes.
I checked the accounts and keep track of it
brigades.
Don't you have anything better to do?
Well. do what you love and you won't
not work a day.
Very funny. Mom. where's my calculator?
I have no idea. Be careful. When you
married and without a job. anything can happen.
Don't worry. I'll figure it out.
Oh yeah? Do you still have headaches?
Yes. but...
This will pass.
I think your body is sending you a signal.
Try to take off yours at least sometimes
suit. Mom. where's my calculator? Not
I know where he is. What you need is
real communication.
Yes? What is he with you now?
No. my dear.
I don't know who you are. nor your face. nor
what are you doing? By the way. you have never
didn’t ask me about my life. No.
asked. And what are my children's names?
Well. your son's name is Busan.
Is this Spider-Man? Sorry. I can't
say Nila.
So it's definitely Spider-Man.
Oh no.
Stolen car. shooting in the streets
Mintown. reinforcements required.
Hey. can you hear? New job for you
lucky. Okay. see you then. Sorry.
I have to go.
Do you want 400 dollars?
Find the 1xbet site. get a bonus for
register and place bets on any
events.
Get in. Spider-Man! No. no. no. no need
she doesn't put it that way.
Hey. watch out!
Everything is fine?
Okay. let's go.
Wait!
You can't tell by just looking at it. but
this street was completely destroyed during
during the Battle of New York.
Come on!
Come on guys!
Yes
ok.
Frank!
Come on. come on!
What the hell. Frank. you just got me
shot down! That's enough. Nat.
We won't do this again. Frank. Of course
we won't!
This time you will get out of the way!
Instead of saving?
You're talking about that shit on Seyton Island again!
No. but you said so.
Crap. Look. you can't just break away.
with a fight. Look. people are suffering.
Who do you think will be in the line of fire?
Get it.
Jerk.
Here it comes.
Oh. hedgehog.
Go home. Frank!
Yes. I will kill this kid.
Yeah. will you stop this thing? She's going to
detention center. I
trying. Look for us on the Internet.
New items are the fastest.
Ultradox. Try better locked there.
a lot of creepy guys.
Who put them there?
Go ahead. Scorpio.
Move.
Hey. what is this?
Okay. everyone come out. He is armed and dangerous.
Get out of the car. ma'am.
I was thinking the same thing.
Spider-Man.
Where am I?
What... Forward!
Let's run. run. run!
It just needs to be cleared from the building.
Have a nice flight. Scorpio!
Well. do you like daylight?
Scorpios are nocturnal.
The building was attacked. Get out of there quickly.
No!
Fly away now! The building is under attack!
Fly! Fly! Fly away quickly!
Alive!
Plans have changed!
Fly with him without me!
What? This is the order! Fly away!
Alive! Fly!
How did you get here?
Spider-Man!
Save me!
Who are you?
You see me.
Tell me who are you?
First you.
You pushed me out.
Interesting. What the hell?
Have you gotten into my head?
No. All the time that you've been behind me
was chasing. you forgot to ask you one very
important question.
What's in the tank?
Spider-Man?
What was that?
I don't know.
Hey. good job.
Hammer. Are you guys okay?
I swear I don't remember doing
any of this.
No problem. no problem. they'll take care of you.
I wouldn't.
Frets? I love you.
Yeah. okay. buddy. okay.
Hey. what do you have?
That's it.
Scorpio was delivered. but the guard took him out
him out the door. What?
What about the tank?
Stolen from a warehouse in Brocklyn.
The driver was a cleaner there.
Is there a motive? Just.
And no criminal record. Scorpio is somehow before him
got there.
Yes. it's possible.
In terms of?
Well. I... I don't know. but... I know the one
who can.
Where are you going?
Practice the leads. I'm with someone
I'll talk.
Hello. is this Breyton 232-50?
You've come to the right place.
Fine.
I think I know what this means.
Take off your clothes.
What?
No clothes are worn in the bathhouse.
Take off your tights.
This is not a tights.
You wrote that this is your office.
This is my office.
Give it here.
Okay. thanks. I just... Haha. my
office. my rules. So we
we can enjoy the pleasant
relaxing swim.
And I see that you don’t have something like that
weapons. and we both win.
Fine.
Seriously? Aren't you going to take this off?
No. it destroys all anonymity.
Even for your girlfriend or something?
There are a lot of guesses about this.
And have you seen super graphic drawings?
The one where you and 10 mysterious... I
I saw. to be honest. it's difficult
unsee. But listen. I don't have anyone.
I'm kind of on my own.
He's alone all the time. I know you're sad.
Well. not so sad.
A little. We could talk about
What did I come here for. huh?
Yes. because this is more your area.
like... small fry.
While the Avengers are focused on
larger bipods.
Yes. I understand. but there's something about it
more. you know? Drivers and
the rest who helped. it looked like
someone speaks to me through them.
It's like someone was looking at me
gulps.
Is this mind control? Exactly.
Used it on me?
Yes. And on others?
Right. No. I don't think so. I think that
it's probably more like
obsession. Who?
Like a ghost or demon. Here in Russia there is
goblin.
The goblin rules the forest and can take over...
Brothers. Whatever it is. they are something
looking for. This is the fourth attack on the facilities
this month.
What do you think they are looking for?
I don't know.
But you know what? After today
attacks appeared interdepartmental
cybersecurity warning.
which worked. Someone gained access
to the closed area.
Using 30 employee credentials
recycling stations. they were all looking for one thing
and the same.
Vimax.
Vimax?
What does it mean?
It could be alien technology
or secret weapons
programs. or startup codes. or... I don't
I know you have to deal with this
figure it out. These are small children's affairs. but
not a job for a big brain. Okay.
ok god. Maybe I'm just there for them
Shall I ask?
I know that I am no longer completely
anonymous
I saw your navel.
Okay. bye.
Hello. I have a meeting with... The Director
Edger. yes. Go through the scanner.
Enhanced Man Discovered.
Superior strength.
Excellent agility. Exacerbated
feeling.
Exogenous DNA.
Arachnid.
Remove the mask for identity scanning.
No. I can't.
Refusal to remove the mask will result in protective
measures.
Protective measures? What do you...
Whoa-woah-woah-woah-woah! Guys. guys
guys! I can't remove the uterus. I
Spider-Man!
Everything is fine.
My apologies.
We're glad you're here.
Bell Metger.
Director Damage Control. How are you?
I'm fine. thanks.
Security had to be beefed up. I hope
didn't scare me.
No. not at all.
Let's pass.
This floor is mainly research.
Below is the elimination of the consequences of the laboratory
and agent training.
What are they doing here?
Everything is fine.
They work for us.
After you brought them. I realized
that this is a group of children without a leader.
They needed guidance. And suddenly
all the things that made them dangerous.
turned them into part of the service
security.
I'm very glad you're here.
You can look at many threats and
see only danger.
Or see opportunities.
Clear.
Wow. look.
In Shocker's hands. this is a nuisance.
But that doesn't mean we can't
learn in these technologies.
Our mission is to redirect
destructive energy.
That's the point of Damage Control.
Be careful. Here.
I wanted to talk about the attacks on
agency. There were four of them. right?
Sit down.
You're right.
Looks like we're facing a threat.
We don't even see her.
And you can.
I saw the camera footage.
And I read Detective Dewolf's report.
I think you understand what we're up against
collided.
Someone or someone can get into the mind
people.
But not yours.
No. I tried. but I couldn't.
I'll be honest.
We are retreating now.
God forbid if it got here and
found what it is looking for. consequences
could be unimaginable.
Let me guess what it is looking for in that
storage. right?
There are things I can't tell you
tell.
But I believe you are the best defense. you
this is the only one.
Lad is immune to this.
I count on you to win.
Good speech. director.
I'll do everything I can.
Then. suddenly. dimage control.
Thank you.
I'll be in touch.
Oh. I wanted to ask.
The phrase Lemax doesn't tell you anything. does it?
No. Where did you hear?
I just... Well. I'm a superhero. right?
things I can't tell.
Anyway. see you later.
Well done. guys. Good luck.
I don't think Luster knows more. but I
I said I would do my best.
Do you want to help? Find Scorpio. He
the only clue.
Yes. yes. I know. Every camera in the city
performs a scan.
Sounds illegal. Spider-Man.
I'll pretend I didn't hear. Yes. yes
it will be better. But if he shows his face. we
we'll find out. Do you have any painkillers?
No. Thank you.
I'll call you back.
Yeah.
Lungs.
Hey. is there something that's highly flammable?
energy?
Yes.
Oh no. no. no. I don't want to. This rubbish
will kill you.
My friends drank them during exams. and
now addicted. So don't sell it to me
them. Remember my face.
Please. Don't sell this guy anything.
similar.
Yes. whatever you say.
I'll take one though.
The last one. Maybe two. And then never
don't sell.
Crap.
Great. dude! Oh hi!
Hello! Order?
Glad to see you! Come on. come in!
Hello. Thank you.
Yes. take it.
Spider-Man was seen in Europe. He
British?
Spider-Man without a mask. This prodigy
parkour is that spider?
I see you came across my board.
I'm not one of those weirdos.
He saved the life of me and my friends in
high school.
Oh cool. Yes. yes. and from then on I just
I'm trying to find out who he is.
Not to expose. just
so that. you know. I hope
thank him face to face.
I created an application that tracks
his appearance.
Have you created a spidey tracker? Did you hear?
Great!
Where is Spider-Man?
Small chat.
We know for sure he's from Queens. Not
biggest discovery. But I managed
narrow down the suspects to two
main ones.
If you knew who they were it would blow
your brain. I'm sure.
By the way. I'm Ned.
I... God. there are 50 people in the apartment.
According to statistics. at least two of them
sociopaths. which is pretty cool.
Beautiful flowers?
Oh. it's... it's... a housewarming gift.
Is it true? Yes.
Oh. okay.
Most brought beer and chips. Cute.
I'm M.J.
I... I... Mein... Meinert.
Oh. you two don't know each other?
No. I'm a neighbor.
Friendly.
Sorry. So. how was the interview?
I'll put the water on.
Nice to meet you. Meinert. Nert. Meynert.
yes.
Sorry. Did you go?
Please tell me you went. Yes. I went.
AND?
I got the job.
God. M.J.. great! I refused.
What? I don't want to be corrupt
corporations.
They are not all corrupt.
Okay. mostly corrupt. But you don't
do you want insurance?
Of course I do.
But at what cost?
It's up to you.
Oh. are you talking about principles? Yes. Sorry.
I don't know. it sounds corny. but...
Something tells me I should wait
something great.
Understand?
Fine.
For waiting for something great.
For waiting.
Well. the wait is over.
Hoo! Ha ha ha!
Dude. this is top class!
Just like you.
I'll hide it.
I forgot it in the hall before the start.
And if Ned needs the fire of a thousand
sharks... Are you talking about tachycardia?
You can't save everyone. But I'll try.
My clever girl.
Let's get motorcycles and live together.
This is great. Yes. I know.
Let's start from scratch and be all together.
Yes. you are right.
A new beginning.
You'll forget who I am.
What? What are you talking about?
Everything is fine.
I will find you anyway and everything to you
I'll explain.
I love you. Wait.
Tell me we'll see you again.
My name is Peter Parker and I would like
one coffee.
Anything else?
Hello. my name is Peter Parker.
I know you don't remember me.
Hello. Do you think that since you have strength. I
can you not listen?
You know. this whole story is scary sometimes
the hell out of me.
Understand?
Yeah. pretty creepy.
Yes.
And everything can change in the blink of an eye.
In ways we cannot even imagine.
Believe me. I know.
Hardly.
How much are you?
Do you want 400 dollars?
Find the 1xbet site. get a bonus for
register and place bets on any
events.
Oh my God!
I live here. I just... So I’ll take yours
things.
Is this my T-shirt?
No.
Oh dear songs.
Hello Peter. You have 107 new ones
notifications.
Look at your watch.
What?
It's starting.
The scan showed a surge in hormones
due to spider DNA. which caused
formation of organic glands.
Receptors are dangerously accelerated.
Okay. but I feel good. This
could have been caused by prolonged isolation
or psychotrauma.
Have you been under a lot of stress recently?
Peter?
I'm fine. Irie. It doesn't look like it. I recommend
take a break and recover.
But I have no choice. right?
Mechanical and organic wapshooter
webs are incompatible.
Come on. Peter.
Anxiety. Overload of the senses.
What the hell was that?
The senses pick up too much
information.
OK. Everything is fine.
Calmly. So yes. organic.
The second Peter succeeded. he was
cool. and so are you.
Oh my God. what disgusting.
Okay. let's go.
Well. it didn't work.
Come on. web. come on. fly out.
Wait. wait. wait.
Wait!
What's up. Evie?
Shots fired outside a data center in Manhattan.
The face matches Scorpio.
Got it. I'm already running.
Come on. three. two... Web!
Web. stop!
Web! So how does it work?
Web!
Sorry. sorry.
Web. stop! Doesn't stop!
Damn. stop. stop. stop. stop!
I don't know what you're looking for. I need
Vimax.
I don't know anything about this. I have to
make sure.
Web. stop!
Sorry. I'm late. It was an easy day
crazy.
Listen. Scorpio. we definitely need this.
do. huh? My head is just pounding.
Do you think I'm a Scorpio?
Web!
What's wrong with you?
Can't you feel me anymore?
What's wrong with you. Spider-Man?
hormone levels increase.
Who are you?
Do you know who you are?
We need help here. I'm coming.
Spider-Man.
What the hell?
Call a doctor.
Is she safe?
Is she okay?
Is she alive? Let me in! No. what's wrong with you?
is that?
This is not Scorpio. clearly. Or rather. he. but they
was controlled by someone from outside. I'm sure of it
sure. Listen. can I... Stop.
slow down.
Listen. I don't know what's happening to you.
but pull yourself together.
You almost killed a cop.
It's not you.
I know. I'm sorry.
One more trick and I won't be able to get you
cover.
Whatever it is. fix it immediately.
Using lattice chromodynamics we
organize time and space into
mesh. which allows us to model
binding of quarks into protons.
Cindy. do you have a question about protons or
again about the Avengers?
Guys. I like to tell stories. but you know.
I actually need to study at least sometimes
you to physics.
Well. please.
OK. Go ahead. Cindy.
If Thanos was worried about
overpopulation. why didn’t I create it?
magic glove more food?
Arthur. will you answer this question?
Hulk. smash!
Great.
Sorry. Dr. Banner. I...
Are you okay? Yes. it's just a headache.
Do you have a minute? I'm talking about yours
inhibitor. Oh
of course.
Don't be afraid. there's a fuse there. so
huge green monster in the dining room
I won't transform. But if you see me without
him. then run.
You are using targeted short
interfering RNA. right?
Like gene suppression. but with
gamma emitter.
What do you say your name is?
No.
Leeds. So you've found a way to suppress
DNA expression even during mutation from
gamma radiation. right?
Yes. Then my question is this.
Will it work DNA that mutates
for another reason?
And what is the reason?
I don't even know. but...
Well. let's say the carrier's genome mixed with
Alien Denko.
Theoretically.
Theoretically. this is quite possible. yes.
Is it possible to suppress the expression leaf?
Denko?
Cut off the bad. leaving only the good.
Like. if I want to keep the Hulk part.
but not everything?
Yes. It would be incredibly dangerous and
difficult. but...
If you aim and hit exactly the right one
strand of RNA. it is possible.
That is. a mutating gene can be turned on
turn off before transcription?
Maybe.
And if you develop this idea. then you can
create an automatic inhibitor.
which will adapt to any mutation.
And now we're talking about universal
inhibitor to control people with
abilities.
Dangerous idea.
Yes. but in theory this is true.
You're not my student. are you?
No. I'm a pirate.
Well. I won't distract you. It's time
return books to the library.
The library is over there.
Exactly. of course.
And how would you decide?
What are you talking about?
In nature. everything has meaning.
What if you're holding back what you need?
give free rein?
Good luck with your studies. Ned.
Thank you. professor.
Spiders are some of the most amazing
creatures in nature.
From birth they are driven by only one thing -
the goal is to survive. But few live to see
maturity. Fourth inhibitor prototype
ready.
So. come on.
Download inhibitor beta 7.
Loaded. Run a test?
Yes. start it.
Spiders go through three life stages
cycle.
Each is accompanied by physical
changes.
The most significant ones occur during
amazing transition to adulthood.
And those who managed to survive it and get through it
this way... Turn off those spider things.
Video disabled.
The inhibitor is active. Let's go. Come on.
come on.
Keep track of the indicators.
The inhibitor has started.
Suppressing spider hormones to baseline levels
level.
Fine.
Either way. we do it.
Launch of the first field test.
Works. Anxiety. Inhibitor
overheats. Functionality drops.
Yes. I feel it.
Anxiety. Overload. Anxiety. Overload
organs.
Spider grenades have been activated.
Oh damn!
First inhibitor test. Failure.
No. Spider-Man!
Are you okay?
Yes. I was just testing the new armor. Ah.
clear.
To get rid of the monster inside.
You don't feel me like that.
Your technology doesn't work.
You know. you're the first person I'm not into
I can... ...settle in.
This joke is probably annoying.
One day I can. What do you need?
I can't understand why
half-man. half-spider decided to work for
office whose goal is to track down
like everyone else.
They are not looking for you because you are different.
They are looking for you because you are dangerous. Yes
what do you need?
Oh. you are such a simple spider.
I'll tell you more simply.
Damage Control has what I need.
Are you talking about Vimax?
I wanted to get everything through Scorpio. but
you're in the way.
Yes. and I will always get in your way. Are you in
Are you sure about this?
Peter Parker.
You know. your apartment looks like a den
sad bachelor. not young
guy. Food containers. dumbbells.
protein powder.
You're bluffing.
You're easy to find. Peter.
Well. at least for someone like me.
But I discovered something interesting. And where
would you think?
On a coffee cup.
Evie. show me the home justice station.
You spent four years erasing Peter Parker from
reality.
No wonder the spider rebelled.
I wonder if MJ even recognizes you?
Perhaps I'll check on her. I don't
I'll allow it.
Her neighbor just kindly posted
new address to the network. What about the tournament
for the race?
Just touch her.
Don't waste your time. I'm fast.
Hey. the smoke is a bit far from here.
Hurry up.
Evie. look for anomalies.
Search for physical anomalies between
objects. Wait.
Thanks everyone for coming.
I'm sorry.
Say hello to Spider. He's running for
love of his life. but so far he is losing.
Come on. Spider. Don't fall behind.
Sorry. sorry.
And you compare the numbers with the rest.
Analyzing the range of jumps.
Give me the data.
I'm calculating.
Come on. I need an answer!
The calculations are complete.
There's a limit to your jump radius
right?
Ten meters.
And where you have no one to inhabit?
Very smart.
I told you. you won't mess with her.
But you're in danger. Where's the neighbor? What? Where
Nick?
But here they are. so what?
Great. come with me. What? What if you don't
spider? I won't go anywhere with you. Time
no. Please. let's go. let's go. Go away
from my house.
Listen. this will sound crazy. but it's up to you
A very dangerous man is hunting. And I. I
promised to protect you.
Please trust me. Please. let's go.
OK.
Don't be afraid.
It's OK.
You'll get used to it.
Are you okay? Yes. everything is fine. Fine.
It's safe here.
From whom is it safe?
I don't know yet.
What do they want from me?
I don't know.
Don't know?
Well. this is nonsense! Why should anyone need me? I would
I wanted to tell you like it is. but...
but... We knew each other. right?
What?
There is no other explanation.
For years I was tormented by why the Spider always
saved me and Ned.
First the Monument. then London. Prague.
over and over again.
Twice is a coincidence. but to
constantly.
We knew each other. am I right?
You're wrong. We were classmates or
friends?
I don't understand what you mean.
Or something more?
It's so strange.
I can't remember if anyone
messed with my brains. and you're the only one.
who knows why.
It's a shame. Mia. I can't. I know that
you can't tell me the truth.
But I need to know.
Maybe some part of me is still
remembers.
Peter. Mary Jane.
I missed you so much.
I can't believe you remembered.
And I can't.
Come on. Peter.
Touch.
Hug.
You've been waiting for this for so long.
True love's kiss breaks the spell and
reunites star-crossed lovers.
Hello Ajin.
Are you really a simple spider?
It's clear why you like her.
She's smart. funny. a little dark and
strange.
It's even sad.
There are no thoughts of you here.
Not a single one.
But you knew that.
You are a monster.
If you loved someone the way I do
I love her. I would know what it is
unforgivable. Oh. that's how it is.
Those who kill have also lost theirs
loved one.
Stop it now.
Your time is running out. Peter.
Soon your friends won't remember Peter anymore
Parker.
Maybe you should write yourself a letter?
Get away from her.
Who is Monster Peter now?
M.J!
M.J! No. no. no. Oh god. oh god
please no. Come on. come on. come on. come on
come on. come on.
Thank God. thank God.
You're okay. you're okay.
I'm so sorry.
Stop. Wait. wait. please. you
won. You won. just don't touch her.
You're just a wreck. Spider.
Anytime I want... I can
be whoever I want.
So you can't defend MJ.
Even from myself.
Very good letter.
A little heavy. Not bad.
Are you okay? I'll take you to safety
place.
What?
Take me to 31-65.
Heading towards the university
The Empire State.
I'm holding you. I'm holding you. Sure?
Okay. I feel like I'm slipping. This
not like that. OK.
You're okay. you're okay. Yes. yes. yes.
I'm fine. fine.
To be continued...
Couldn't you have seen this coming? Yes what
is it wrong with you? You could have killed us.
Sorry. you show up at my house without
warnings. What was the calculation? What.
is this your house?
Wait. wait. Who else is this?
Who are you?
She. well. you know.
No. I don't know. that's why I asked.
She's in danger. Frank. I need yours
help. okay?
Yes. it looks like it. Come on. I have you
debt. Come on. I'm not tired of this
history. That nylon.
Yes. that same nylon. What do you want.
what should I do? I literally saved yours
life. Yes. you beat me! I have to save her
twice for you to help me. That guy
could have hit me with a handful of rice. On
what does it look like? I had him exactly
where I wanted. I saw him there. I
I just knew where I needed him. And he told me
That's how I decided now. Okay. okay.
go ahead. I will remember it all my life.
I don't care. I just want to go home.
This is a great idea. Flag in hand. go
home.
Wait. Prank. Prank. wait.
Please.
I have to keep her safe and I have nowhere else to go
go.
Do you like chili?
I made chili.
Okay. just be careful with the mines. I don't
I want to collect your pieces in the next two
weeks.
I definitely wouldn't eat his chili.
You say that the maniac behind everything
this nonsense with the tank. it's nothing else.
like some teenager? It's not only
tank. and every attack on Damage
Control for the past month. Where from
does the child know how to drive a tank? I
I don't know. Frank.
Girl kicked your ass? Kicked
my ass.
Yes. Is this your family?
Could you please move the fuck away?
I have one rule in this house. You
You don't touch anything.
You don't move anything. and you certainly
damn. don't ask me any questions
no questions about anything.
So. three rules.
That's why you like her.
Go for a day in tons.
Don't touch Chile!
I like him.
Of course I like it.
In general. I managed to pull out
image from my interface and
run through the system.
Who is she?
Until a couple of months ago... no one.
She was in foster care. out of foster care. in
mental hospitals. and then she
escaped and disappeared from radar. on her
there is almost no information that is not
erased. but it is classified as
telepath. And now we have a name.
Jane Gray.
Yes. These are damage control objects. on
which she has not yet attacked.
So if she shows up. it's mine
face tracking software will detect it.
Clear. Oh yeah? What then?
Look. don't worry about what happens next.
Just take a closer look. Don't worry
Yes? I just have to babysit yours
girl. I don't want that with me
babysat Okay. listen. what's the plan. huh?
Just hope it's yours
Does face tracking work?
They will kill you. and I have to look after her
all my life. They won't kill me. Frank. I can
catch her. okay? I just need
fix the inhibitor and then I will
ready. What do you need for this?
Frank. you don't have what I need.
for this. okay?
I don't whisper either. So what do you have
there is an antistatic mat. tonal
umbrella and microtools?
I have this shit.
For what?
Bomb. Bingo.
Do you think it would be safe to call
someone and tell me I'm okay?
To your boyfriend?
No. like my neighbor.
I don't think it's that good
idea. just... She already knows who it is
who. and she can share with whom
wants to. so... Right. yes.
Yes. yes. yes. you're right.
Sorry. No. it's okay. I'm okay
I understand.
About my boyfriend.
He'll just ask me a bunch of questions...
which I cannot answer.
He'll say I'm being secretive again.
Are you being secretive? Yeah.
It sounds like your boyfriend is an asshole.
And why does he think that?
I don't know.
You tell me. mass vigilante for
backstage.
Okay. I understand what you mean.
About you.
Maybe drive through.
Well. do you have Mrs. Spider-Man?
Do I have Mrs. Spider-Man?
No. No. I... Why not?
Why not. because... Obviously
I'm too secretive.
Welcome to the club.
Some people were.
Is it true? Yes. yes. yes.
What's happened?
I... I had to let her go.
To keep her alive.
I don't know. it must be very hard.
Yes. that's what happened.
This is true.
Yes. it's hard.
Are you okay?
Yes. yes. yes. I'm fine. You know what. I
I'll just come over. Wait. wait.
wait. wait.
What's happened?
He just keeps getting burned out.
I've been suffering for several days now.
Yes. aerospace. I
was going to biochemical engineering.
Do you mind if... Yes. of course. that's it.
Fine.
Self-organization. it generates some kind of
radiation or magnetic field because
it would definitely get in the way.
Yes. it has a micromagnetic field. but
I took this into account in the project.
Okay. what about your suit? Oh
it actually dissipates into the tissue. which
pretty cool.
OK.
What about them?
About what?
Your glasses.
Or whatever you call them? They would
created a field. it would be tiny.
but... But they are on your head. which is very
close to the inhibitor.
This is probably the reason. Oh MJ
this is brilliant.
Okay. this should work.
Inhibitor on.
Suppression of selected hormones
arachnids.
Okay. that's better.
This is definitely better.
Oh. my head is fresh.
I don't shoot organic poutine. God
my. Amy. it absolutely worked.
What you're working on here is very...
serious things.
But yes. it's really important.
Yeah. but it's. I mean. it's like
changing your DNA.
I want to say this is what you need
put it on. I don’t know. for example. on a monster.
Well. if you could see what's wrong with me
has been happening over the last couple
days. then you might understand.
I've been with you for several hours and it's not
what I saw.
Well. what did you see?
On my side. the curtain.
Just a nice guy who.
maybe it's just changing.
I don't want to cross boundaries. I'll let you
you get back to work.
Hello. my name is Peter Parker.
You can’t shut up either. huh?
Would you like some coffee?
Certainly.
Did you fix your thing?
Yes. I wore it all night. That's all for now
ok.
I made another universal one.
So if I can put it on gin.
this should completely dampen her powers.
I know it would work. Shoot a bullet
in the forehead.
Cool.
Dear God. this must be the most
stupidest crap I've ever
saw. You can't even take off your mask
to have a cup of coffee.
Don't take it personally. Frank. She
remains on me for everyone.
Even for her?
Who is she. guy?
Don't know.
This is bullshit. Who is she? I'm telling you
I don't know who she is.
You know. You care about her. but you don't
you take care of her. I don't know who she is
like that. Frank. I have no one. I'm like
you. I just keep to myself. How are you
me?
What do you know about me. boy?
Do you think it's a choice to live like this? This
way of life? So do you think?
Master. this is a sentence!
Listen. if only for a second people
that I love would still be alive.
Do you think I would hide behind a mask?
Do you think I would pretend to be someone I'm not?
am I? Would you act like a damn coward?
There is a coincidence of epics.
She's at damage control headquarters on
Manhattan. I have to go. OK?
She'll be fine.
I'll take care of it.
Thank you Frank.
Hello.
Will you let him go alone?
I think he might need you.
How do you like it in Streeton Thailand?
Vi Max.
Nothing found.
You can't hide from me forever
Bill.
Your door is strong. but I wouldn't
have a lot of hope for her.
Who are you and what do you need?
I'm Ginny Gray.
And you know what I want.
Gin?
Were you looking for me?
I'm blushing.
I told you that it will be your girlfriend if
you will interfere.
You won't go near her again.
And you definitely won’t get into the storage room.
Maybe not.
But here he is. yes.
Jean. you don't know what you're up to.
You know. you and Banner have a lot in common.
Both are engaged in a fierce battle with the monster that
lives inside you.
Jane. it's the Hulk. You can't do it like this.
Didn't understand.
Oh. exactly.
Do you want to shut my mouth just like you?
I can't let you in.
Whatever Vimac is. you won't get it.
I was daydreaming. Oh damn!
Gin. don't.
Less words.
What are you doing here? In terms of? I'm saving
you!
This is generally not your level at all. You
shot at the hulk. Oh damn!
Seriously?
Back off! Yes. good shooting! How are you
I'm sick of it already!
Banner. no problem. it's all fucked up!
I told you to keep an eye on MJ. Yes.
said.
And she told me to keep an eye on you.
Wait. did she really say that?
You're not blushing there. okay?
Let me not blush.
Damn it. I should have taken a gun
more.
Ah. super bigger. So what. would you
finished him off?
No. in short. we change the plan.
We hook it to the Hulk. then we go after
Gin.
I have a better idea.
The Hulk is a deadly threat. You are his
If you hold back. I’ll cut down more sources.
It's clear? Do you want to roll back from a fight with
Hulk?
Something like that. Okay. no matter. I can handle it.
Oh Frank. Frank! What?
Don't kill her!
Come on. no vanilla snot!
If I do something. I always
in my own way. Go. go. go already!
Don't go within a kilometer of her. Ah-ah-ah!
I'm already sick of it.
I'm good. good. good.
Oh no.
Not again.
Dr. Banner. is that you?
Spider-Man. What's happened? Where am I?
I did all this? Yes. Did I hurt someone?
It's okay. it's okay. it's her
controlled you. I lost my inhibitor.
Here. here. here. Only he holds the monster
inside.
It's okay. I have another one. put it on
him. What is this?
It's universal and should help.
I'm asking you. yes. they are people. put it on.
Everything is fine?
Head. She broke something.
Is she still there? No. this is a different me.
Bruce. I can get you out. okay?
Just put on the inhibitor. Get away from me!
Enough. I can't handle him.
You can do it. Bruce. you can do it. Get out of here!
Get out of the building!
Everyone get out of the building!
Run!
Run! Run! Banner. please hold on.
No. Peter. it's late.
This is the Hulk.
I didn't know how big you were.
Well. good luck to you. Peter.
There you are.
Don't move. don't move. Ah.
damn
No combat.
The countdown has started.
Face recognition. Dangerous. Weapons and
glove.
90 seconds before the explosion. Yes. I know. I know.
What kind of skin do you have?
No inhibitor attached. Let's!
Dr. Bennett. please.
Enough. This is Peter.
I'm your friend.
Give it up... And now?
Why are payouts always faster at 1xbet?
me?
Let's bet again.
Guns while the heads are intact.
Where is she?
What are you... It's over. Jean.
This is my gun!
Is anyone injured?
Because of me?
Spider-Man!
You saved my life.
I saved God knows how many lives. because I didn’t
let her find what she was looking for.
She was trying to tell me something.
Name Sarah.
Does this mean anything to you?
Until you put on the inhibitor. she's on
momentarily penetrated my mind.
Sarah. That was the name of the person I was with
was close not long ago.
I'm really sorry.
Somehow remembering Sarah
influenced her.
I would talk to her when she wakes up.
if possible.
Certainly. She will be transferred to our complex at
Rootvelt Island.
I really want to forgive myself
her. But for one day this is already too much.
Yes. sure.
Thank you. Spider-Man. My pleasure.
Hey Jay.
It worked. She's in custody. Everything is fine.
Did you want me to find it?
No. No.
I can explain. Please take it off.
What?
Mapku.
I think I have the right to talk about this with
Peter Parker.
You came to the party then.
To the donut shop.
The year I left.
Why didn't you say it then?
I wanted to protect you.
But over the last day I was barely five times
they didn’t kill you. so this is how you cope
to yourself. I know. I'm sorry. I...
Did you even want to tell me?
OK.
So. you just decided everything for me.
I know. I'm sorry.
I don't need your constant apologies.
I don't know what you want to hear. A
why did you do this to me?
This someone would still be alive if it weren't for me.
I didn't tell you because... I didn't.
I wanted the same thing to happen to you.
But this is not for you. Reysan. I know it
but... you... you are everything to me.
I tried to somehow live without you. but... I
I can't.
I love you.
Is this a spell?
Or what did you do to me?
It worked.
All these memories of ours that you are talking about
you say I have...
I don't have any.
And I understand why she could love
you.
The one you wrote the letter to. but...
I understand.
You did what you had to do for her
protection.
And for that I am grateful.
But I...
I don't love you.
It's just that I don't even... I don't know you.
I guess it's best for me to leave.
I'm really sorry. Bitter.
I don't have a phone.
Maybe
will you take me home?
Certainly. Thank you.
Thank you. Yes. sure.
I then... Yes. yes. of course.
Do you want to go up?
Just might as well say hello at this point.
With pleasure.
Hulk. aka Dr. Bruce Banner. is taken under
guard.
He is now being transferred to a psychiatric hospital.
department.
Sadness. After many years of peaceful scientific
life today the whole world is set by one
question. What ended up breaking?
Hey. I'm right here.
Hey. I'm right here. Andzhey? Yes?
Hey. I'm right here. You won't believe it. Hey I
it's nearby. But the spider tracker says that
Spider-Man is out there now
nearby.
Yes. wow. amazing. Hey. I'm here
Hey. I'm right here.
Um. Ned. Spider-Man. Spider-Man.
Week
Very nice. Ned.
Actually. I'm not some kind of weirdo.
A little bit. Why?
Why are you here?
Well. I... I was... She was on
platform. yes. Yes. and... Stuck in
phone. Yes. I got distracted. and here comes
train. And I just snatched it.
Yes. you fell me.
My God!
Why doesn't this happen to me?
What if you're flying on a web and you
you need to pee and you just
landing on the roof? What?
Or you go downstairs. run into a store.
and I’m like. I’m Spider-Man. where’s the toilet? Or
Can you still find the roof? No I'm not looking
no roofs.
Is that the only thing you're interested in now?
Yes. listen. ask anything.
Tell me how I shoot Putina. A
Actually. I already know this.
Seriously? Well. there's clearly something wrong there
Newtonian fluid. which
circulates in the chamber to maintain
liquid form. And when you activate them
by pressing the triggers. it goes through
styphon turbine. and then hardens
in the air.
Yes?
Well. kind of. well. not quite like that. but okay.
then what does a web consist of? I
I guess from somewhere
long chain polymer. Um. nylon.
Yes. not bad. good. good. but how
about... Or is it Nomex or
Kevlar?
Okay. keep your secrets.
If you notice the dragon incident. I
I’ll support you. Sumov.
All I did was give it a little push
your uncle to the exit.
Cool reference. Oh
time for banh mi. Did you order banh mi?
As many as five pieces. We have a man at home
-Spider. you need to feed him.
I'm sorry. he's just really happy
that you are here.
Are you serious? I haven't had this much fun in ages.
I think I miss you.
You really look like best friends.
In terms of?
Tell him.
He can handle it.
Yes. I know.
But... When she was in your head.
there.
on the roof. she kissed me and I
replied. Just
I thought it was you. but I didn’t know.
And I... I'm really sorry.
I decided to tell you.
Thank you for saying that.
It’s like I don’t remember anything anyway.
so... Really?
Yes.
It was strange. I was just sitting at the table.
and a second later she was already lying on the street.
I don’t know. it’s like the lights have been turned off.
What? Don't you remember anything?
No. what?
Matt Gurd said he was thinking about someone
named Tarat. and says that you don’t remember
nothing at all.
Well. yes. everything happened instantly. from this
and so scary.
He lied to me.
They say you caught Blassie. Yes. her name is
Jean Grey. I need you to find out
drying size. Drying? It's about black
widow. I think Matt Gurd lied to me about
name. Can you check if there is a connection?
between Jean and someone named Sarah?
Hmm. a little small fry.
Wow. is this really your office?
Yes. yes. yes. On the Internet.
government archives have a lot of data.
related to Jean Grey.
They were cleared.
Damage control.
Data about what?
About her sister.
Does Jean have a sister?
Yes. Sarah Gray.
Also a telepath.
Damage control took her into custody for
study and observation.
Wow. he actually knows what that means.
Yes. exactly.
Wait. who are you?
Hi Ned Leeds. yes.
Hello. And I... Oh. sorry.
I'm very glad that our poor guy has
friends.
Thank you
I... I owe you.
Good luck. Spider-Man. Bye.
She was just looking for her sister and I gave her away
to the people who took her.
I have to go.
Peter?
Be careful. okay?
Fine.
Spider-Man's name is Peter?
Who will you be?
Her. In pink.
She's far away.
Need to jump.
Jump? Choose someone closer.
And then...
Jumping has a limit. but if you tie
them. you can go anywhere.
And when you let go. you will return to the beginning.
And this can be done with everyone in this
park?
Maybe someday. if you learn.
How could she just kick us out?
She was not our mother.
Well. not in that sense. Was. Before
we have changed. Well. if it's that simple
give up the role of mother. then what are you
mother?
What if you had daughters like
us?
I would love them.
Especially the redhead.
Shut up!
We have us.
Will you have chocolate? Yes.
That's how you play.
Live to the ground! To the ground!
Get down on the ground immediately!
Old!
Sorry. Gin.
I have to protect you.
The object woke up. Pulse 94 beats per
minute.
Jean. this won't work anymore. Thank you
To Spider-Man.
Gin?
Breathe. Look at me and breathe. Fine.
You're safe. Breathe.
Where is she?
Like your sister. you were given power.
capable of bringing great benefit to the world.
Or huge destruction.
Power like you have in the hands of a child.
an unbearable burden.
But imagine if she was in your hands
those who know how to manage it.
Where is my sister?
You will change the world. Jen!
Hey!
I know where you are and what you are doing. Oh well. and
where from?
I've got eyes everywhere. boy.
Listen. Frank. Damage Control has been kidnapped.
sister Jean. She tried to find her. We
We were wrong about everything.
Sentimental nonsense.
Have you seen what she can do. what she can do?
capable.
Seriously. so what?
Are you going to help her?
If you do this I will deal with her
in my own way. Frank. please. Damage
Control... Yes... Frank!
Checking the distance. 12 meters. Blocking
room. We block.
Disable inhibitor.
Jen. your abilities are now working
full force.
As you can see...
We're outside your jump radius.
Tell me. what is V-Max?
You're the second one to ask.
I have no idea what this is.
She sent me a message.
I tried to help find her.
She communicated with you telepathically on
such a distance.
And it caused a huge splash
activity.
Amazing. What does that mean. idiot?
I don't know.
Let's get started.
Our work with Sarah covered two
regions. Finding the source of her power and
looking for a way to copy it.
If we could record telepathic
brain while jumping. then they could
reproduce these paths in consciousness by
our choice.
This device is your sister's legacy.
We created it together over months of testing and...
errors.
I hope we can honor her sacrifice.
What are you talking about?
Forget the first jump.
Tell me what Vimakt is. I know that
you hide it there.
She is jumping.
Accepted. Complete blocking.
The process has started.
What process?
Hey. wow. you look so serious
dude.
Hey. hey. what the hell. man. I'm a friend
Damage Control. What are you doing. well?
Hmm. so you want to fight?
Okay. okay. just a second.
Give me a second.
I'm not a schoolboy anymore after all.
Join us if you like stretching. For
your work is important.
Are you guys working out?
This is so helpful.
Are you ready?
Watch your head!
Where is Jean Gray?
Jump 26.
The records are in order. Sorry. sir.
Invasion of the facility.
You're right. She is not stronger than her sister.
Increase the frequency.
You're doing great. G.
To be continued...
Gin? Jean. can you hear me?
Gin?
You are a killer!
Its frequencies change.
This can't be true.
The last one! What my sister saw was
this room.
Brain waves affect objects around you
her.
Disable. I'm trying. sir. What does it mean
are you trying?
The last thing she saw was fucking
room!
Turn it off! I can't. sir.
I can't let you. Bill.
This power...
Only I will be in charge.
What do you want?
Jean. I'm here to help you.
It's because of you that I'm here.
Yes. and I'm sorry about Sarah that I do.
I was wrong.
If you came to save a helpless girl
from damage control. then you're too late.
It is them who need to be saved.
And now you too.
Let's go God this is cool
Jane. please!
It's funny. isn't it?
Friends from Damage Control made a special
a weapon just for you.
They have a whole squad ready.
If you suddenly get out of hand...
People are monsters.
Don't trust them more than they do
trust you.
I'm a little busy. Frank.
Trouble. boy!
We need to keep everyone a kilometer away from
islands.
Wait. what?
If you want to do something. do it
now! I'm trying.
My sister died in this room. in
surrounded by these people.
And her only fault was that she
special.
Just like you.
Just like me.
People like us are not allowed to live a normal life.
life.
We can't have friends or family.
They all left.
The old life is over.
Maybe you'll be honest with yourself.
Are you Peter Parker?
Or are you Spider-Man?
Both.
Jane. please.
It won't fix anything.
Bro. you're not a killer. Jane. You have no idea
you know who I am.
I know you loved your sister.
And I know that having lost her. you feel like
lost everything.
If you come closer. he will die! They all
will die!
You know it won't bring her back. Jean.
Do you think your mind is inaccessible to me?
I got stronger from my last try.
Let's. Hello.
Hello.
Do you think you can not listen to me. since
have you gained strength?
You know...
It can be very scary.
Understand?
This is already quite scary.
Yes. And everything can change.
Very fast. Just as we imagine
we can't.
I understand.
I think not completely.
What are you talking about?
You are a very special person.
I hope this helps you evaluate yourself.
But I know that sometimes this is not the case.
Sometimes you will feel very lonely.
And sometimes. because you are special. people
can commit
terrible. monstrous acts
towards you.
But I want you to remember one thing.
You are beautiful.
And the people who love you don't love you
because you are special. but because
you are you.
And I want you to remember this.
Even when it seems like you're all alone.
This is your main responsibility.
Never forget how strong you are
neither did.
I'm sorry about your sister.
I'm sorry about your aunt.
Yes. you would love her.
Just because we lost someone doesn't mean
that we should be alone.
It won't work that way.
Believe me. I tried.
It doesn't work.
Even if it's true. I have no one
no.
You have me.
I'm fine.
Peter. I'm fine. fine. Peter.
no!
Peter. Peter!
No. no. no!
Peter!
Get out of here. they will look for you.
No. no. no. no. please stay with
me. come on. hold on. please! Gin. you
you'll be fine.
Just go.
Look at me.
The elusive defender of the city in critical
condition. Doctors are fighting for his life.
The whole city is watching fate
Spider-Man.
A hero who saved New York only once.
now in the hands of the best specialists.
And New Yorkers held their breath.
Frank. Where am I?
No. no. no. no. no. no. Where is mine
mask? Don't worry. I got it all sorted out. Are you in
ok. Where's Jane? Is she safe? Yes. she's in
ok. She's fine. Where is she?
She recently left.
She conjured her Voodoo there so that you
didn't die.
Yes. She's fine.
Sorry.
I'm very sorry for what I did. That.
what happened to you is terrible.
I saw it.
I have seen many brave men.
For your life.
But this... It was something incredible.
Are you crying?
No no.
And you know. I'm about the same as you and
represented.
You're a good guy.
I didn't have such a friend.
We're friends now.
I can't believe I saw you
you cry. Well. that's enough. What are you talking about?
Nonsense.
Oh yes.
They stood there all night. From the moment
they brought you. Take a look.
You went to take off your suit. but when
When you're ready to leave. I have a plan.
Room 2-1-4-9. come here.
It's Spider-Man!
We love you!
Hello!
You're the best. Spider-Man!
We love you. Spider-Man!
Spider-Man!
You are our hero!
Come back! We love you!
You are the best! You are our hero! You are our hero!
Spider-Man!
May Parker.
By helping one. you help everyone.
I... I've thought a lot about your words.
And you'll be glad to know that I've decided... I
I won't be alone anymore.
I miss you. May.
Well. my back still hurts a little. but I
I could go out if you need anything else
need to. I need you to rest.
Yes. I know. I know. but give me something.
By the way. how is the investigation going?
Well. Mattsger is still missing. But yours
friend. Black Widow. helps us
dig through the records.
which damage control tried to erase.
I stopped by her office the other day. Yes? And
how is it?
Well. the skin is amazing now.
Attention to all posts. Confirmed
bank robbery.
And do you hear it?
Yes. I'll do it.
It's not far. I could drive up.
No. we can handle the robbery.
Just take care of yourself.
OK.
You too.
Say hi to Jay and Marley.
Fine.
Spider-Man says hi.
Hello. Oh. hi.
Oh. wow. boy. With flowers. right? C
parties.
I'm Peter.
Okay. hi.
Peter!
Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm